<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management | Hamed Mehranfar</title>
    <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/tag/management/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/tag/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Management</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/media/icon_hua6ea50ac1e7d6c97b2bdc61d61b09274_89624_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Management</title>
      <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/tag/management/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop with Track management team @SBB!</title>
      <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/post/2024-01-26-workshop-with-track-management-team-sbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/post/2024-01-26-workshop-with-track-management-team-sbb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, we had a productive workshop with the SBB track management team. We introduced our methodology to estimate intervention requirements, their costs, and required possession windows in the early phases of the intervention planning process. The workshop was well-received and we had a very good discussion afterwards. We exchanged feedback and ideas on how to improve and adapt this work to the specific needs and challenges of the SBB network. I am looking forward to working more closely with the SBB team to find the best ways to implement this work and support their decision making in the intervention planning process.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated early estimation of bridge interventions, possession windows and costs</title>
      <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/publication/journal-article-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/publication/journal-article-5/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Fleet Allocation</title>
      <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/project/smart-fleet-allocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/project/smart-fleet-allocation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project a a digital tool was developed for improving the decision making about the taking different operation policies on how to dispatch and distribute the cargo wagon across the railway network in Iran. The project employed a mixture of optimization models and data analysis to provide optimal solutions for various scenarios for minimizing operational costs, maximizing availability of wagons. The project delivered a user-friendly interface using &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anylogic.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;AnyLogic©&lt;/a&gt; that helps the decision makers in planning and executing the fleet allocation strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cargo for Rail</title>
      <link>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/project/cargo-for-rail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://hamedmehranfar.github.io/project/cargo-for-rail/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project a a decision aiding tool was developed for improving the decision making about the taking different operation policies on how to improve the efficiency of operations related to logistics of mineral cargo with rail. The project analyses the current situation and assessed multiple improvement policies using discrete event simulation in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.interdynamics.com/decision-support-software-solutions/planimate-simulation-software/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Planimate©&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
